I thought she had completely
erased me from her life.
I resented her for so long, Enzo.
You're cute, huh?
You even understand my craziness.
It's like you always know
what to say when I get dramatic.
But seriously. You want to give it a try?
Yes?
-It's for our Entrepreneurship Week.
-Ah.
I wanted to invite you there.
Those bastards!
They're intimidating me again.
-I'll call the police then.
-No, no. I have to go.
-I have to go to Patricia.
-Relax. She will come, okay?
Miss D said she's on her way.
We still have 30 minutes left.
-Patricia!
-Mama.
You came.
Good morning.
Diana.
-Ricardo.
-I've been waiting.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
-Mama?
Flowers for you.
-Thank you.
-This bouquet is a token
of appreciation from our school.
Please send my thanks, dear.
You made me worry.
I wish you had waited for me.
I could have given you a ride.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ricardo.
But it would've been too late.
I was in a hurry.
I'm sorry.
Uh, Patricia, please don't get me wrong.
Uh…
All I care about is your mom's safety.
We still don't know
who's behind those threats.
What's going on?
Nothing. Ricardo and I just have
something to talk about.
See you later, okay?
Mama's still receiving threats.
She hasn't mentioned anything to me.
I think she and Ricardo
are keeping it a secret.
But… haven't they already decided
Sir Teddy is the suspect?
I talked to Uncle Teddy.
I know he's not to be trusted.
But something tells me otherwise.
What if he was telling the truth?
I'm trying to piece together how and where
it all started.
You know…
everything had been going smoothly
since I started working here
in La Familia.
There had been no critical concerns
or major issues.
It all began
with the food poisoning incident.
Oh. That caused her
a lot of stress, right?
It eventually led to her
having a heart attack.
Mm-hmm. And Sir Ricardo's
blaming Sir Teddy for that.
A driver is testifying against him.
Which Uncle Teddy denies.
Plus, there was not enough
evidence against him.
Soon after,
a video about the old fire went viral.
It's as if they want to remind everyone
of what happened back then,
and of what Miss D has been concealing.
And so the media has been
more relentless against Miss D.
Her leadership has become questionable.
But it's still not confirmed
who actually posted the video.
When the video about Grandma came out…
They wanted to make it seem
like Mama's not okay.
Basically, they want to bring Miss D down.
To make everyone think:
Like mother, like daughter?
That Miss D was the one who
started the fire at the factory?
You know, all of these things
are rooted in the past.
Miss D is being haunted by the past.
The fire in La Familia.
That's what we need to uncover.
What exactly happened in the past?
They can't bury the hatchet!
Hey, watch out!
You almost hit me!
I thought you were working
to keep them from reconciling.
That's why you've been getting
close to Patricia, right?
So you can poison her mind against Diana,
and Diana will run to you when they fight.
As long as I'm around,
they'll never settle their differences.
Diana isn't allowed to be happy.
Is this how it's going to be?
You still don't understand why I did that.
I just didn't want Diana
to think even less of you.
She already looks down on me.
And the only reason I took the money
was because I knew you needed it.
I had to swallow my pride.
That's why I didn't tell you and Patricia.
Anything else you're hiding from me?
No.
Nothing.
That's why I feel so hurt.
You know…
No matter how hard things were,
we were happy as a family.
But ever since Diana came back
into our lives,
everything has fallen apart.
Why do you let Diana affect you so much?
You don't understand how I feel!
It's like…
I was given something that…
could be taken away at any moment.
-I chose you.
-Did you really choose me?
Or did you end up with me
only because Diana let you go?
Carlota, we've been together
for a long time.
We'll never fix this
if you keep thinking that way.
I'm here, with you.
Please don't make me feel
like that's not enough.
Martin…
I can't bear to lose you.
To lose you and our daughter.
Take away this fear from me.
Give me that one thing
you haven't given yet.
Maybe I'd be calmer when you do.
I love you so much.
These are all inventory reports,
delivery receipts,
and accounting records.
I also searched the internet,
but couldn't find anything.
It seems like all the news
about the fire is gone.
Did you see something?
Mommy! Mommy!
Are you okay?
Hm.
Uh…
It's my mom.
You know…
I often imagine…
What if the fire never happened?
What if they're still alive?
I'm sure I'll always treat them
to something.
That's how they were with me back then.
You know, I believe…
They're very happy with where you are now.
They can see everything
you're doing for La Familia.
My loyalty to La Familia…
My loyalty to Miss D…
I do all that for them.
I just know they're very proud of you.
After all, you're not only
a great employee.
You're also a very kind person, Enzo.
Thank you.
Wait.
I remember something.
When I was a kid…
Mommy always brought home
documents from the office.
If I'm right,
there are documents
that weren't burned by the fire.
And to this day, those documents
are still hidden.
Head of Corporate Communications,
Nestor Manikan.
Nestor Manikan…
Did you see anything?
Nestor Manikan.
His name sounds familiar.
I'm near Nestor Manikan's listed address.
I'll just ask around.
I feel like he really knows
something about the fire.
Are you sure?
Well, I have nothing to lose if I try.
Okay. Be careful.
I'm sorry I couldn't come with you.
Miss D has an important meeting
this morning.
It's fine.
I'll keep you updated, okay?
All right, bye.
Ma'am?
Sorry. Excuse me.
Do you know a Nestor Manikan?
Nestor? I don't know him, sorry.
All right, thank you.
Uh, excuse me.
Why are you looking for my father?
My name is Patricia.
Are you Diana's daughter?
I just wanted to ask something.
Sure. What…
can I help you with?
What do you know about the fire back then?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I have no ill intentions.
I just want to know the truth.
Miss D was very kind to our family.
We owe Papa's life to her.
She even paid for Papa's therapy!
Ever since I was a child,
I have had a lot of questions.
Especially about my family.
And I have never gotten
an answer until now.
Mister Nestor…
There is a reason you're given
a second chance at life.
Maybe it's time for you to tell the truth.
I don't want…
…to ruin someone's life.
What if your silence has
already ruined someone's life?
Is that what happened to you, Patricia?
Was your life ruined?
Why me?
What do you mean?
I just followed Diana's orders.
What I did was for you.
Oh, Patricia.
-Go on in.
-Dear.
-What are you doing here?
-I'll prepare some snacks.
What's wrong?
I spoke to your former employee,
Nestor Manikan.
What did you make him do?
Nothing.
Why did you cover up
what happened in the fire?
That's the only reason I can think of
why you don't want to revisit the past.
-Patricia.
-What did you do?
Did you really burn down La Familia?
Don't you…
Don't you remember
anything about the fire?
Did you light the candle at the factory?
Patricia, tell me. What did you do?
Are you still blaming me for it?
No!
-I had nothing to do with it!
-Patricia!
I didn't burn down the factory!
Why did you have to lie?
-Why?
-To protect you!
All the evidence
against Patricia has been erased.
So it'll all point to Cecilia Pineda.
Make sure nothing about this gets out.
Do you understand why I had to do this?
You don't have to explain it to me,
Ma'am Diana.
I'm a parent, too.
I'm not a bad person.
But I couldn't bear to see
my daughter's life ruined.
You're the only one I can trust.
No one can know that
Patricia was at the factory
when the fire happened.
To protect you!
I knew they'd keep looking
for someone to blame
for what happened.
And because you're an Aragon,
you'd be the easiest target.
I knew they'd include you
in the investigation.
And I couldn't risk them destroying you
just so they could close the case.
It's clear to me now.
I didn't start the fire.
I saw it myself.
The candle I lit wasn't
where the fire started!
And I believe you!
You didn't do it!
None of this is your fault, dear.
M-my whole life…
I thought you blamed me
for Grandpa's death.
Oh, my god. No, dear. No.
Dear, no.
-No, no!
-Diana?
Patricia?
What's going on here?
Patricia and I were just talking.
Could you please leave us alone for now?
No.
Patricia, are you fighting
with your mother again?
What do you think she did this time?
Patricia, Diana's doing everything she can
to get closer to you.
You probably don't see it
because she just has
a different way of showing it.
You think she's cruel.
You think she doesn't care about you.
But your mother loves you
more than anything.
Ricardo…
Dear, let's talk another day, okay?
Dear…
Let's go.
Why did you bring me here?
Because you need it.
-I think this is a bad idea.
-Diana…
I just left Patricia like that.
You both need to take a breath.
What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
I don't know if I should be here.
Diana.
I don't have to know what you
and Patricia talked about.
I just want to help you clear your head
and make your problems go away.
Just let it out.
It's okay.
I won't leave you, Diana.
No matter what happens.
Everyone else might leave,
but I'll always stay by your side.
Ricardo…
What's wrong?
We shouldn't have done it.
Diana, come on.
Even just for a day…
I just want to be happy with you.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
I'm just built this way.
Whatever you are…
my feelings for you won't change.
-Can I ask you a favor?
-Sure.
I hope you understand, but…
I hope that no one knows about this.
I don't want to complicate things.
I understand.
I mean…
you're the boss.
What happened to your back?
It was my father.
-I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
I'm sorry.
-Thank you, Clara.
-Okay, ma'am.
Here are…
the memos that need your signature.
About what happened…
All my life…
I've carried this heavy burden.
I thought…
you blamed me for the fire.
you blamed me
for all the bad things
that happened to our family.
No, Patricia.
I'm sorry if that's what I made you feel.
I was just…
I was grieving back then.
I couldn't process my emotions properly.
I'm sorry, dear. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
I'm sorry, Mama.
But you know,
even though the investigation was closed,
it still haunts me.
The past continues to haunt me.
Why should you be the one to pay for it?
You should've just let
the investigation continue.
Then we would've found out the truth.
Patricia…
I'll take anything they throw at me…
as long as your life doesn't get ruined.
Mama… I'm not going to stop trying
to find out the truth.
We can still make things right.
Especially now that your life
is in danger.
You're being threatened
because they're blaming you.
Patricia, let the police
do their job. Okay?
Ricardo is already helping us
find whoever's threatening me.
That's right.
We need to find out who's behind it.
Could it be someone seeking revenge
for what happened in the fire?
What about… Cecilia?
Could she have something to do with this?
Don't you want to know the truth?
Patricia, please stop.
Let me handle this.
I won't let you get hurt.
It can't be Cecilia.
She's dead.
Do you think she really started the fire?
That's what the investigation concluded.
What if it wasn't her?
Maybe your lead is wrong, Patricia.
If Cecilia wasn't the one
who started the fire at La Familia,
it could only mean one thing.
It means my parents
still haven't gotten justice.
I had Ricardo investigated.
I'm sorry.
But as I've said, if you have
an issue with Sir Ricardo,
don't drag me into it.
He said he has a child,
with no record to prove it.
He said he's married,
but it was not registered.
In all of his employment records,
he wrote his civil status as "Single."
He told me he was never married.
But there are no traces
of a family in his records.
I also initiated
a digital footprint investigation.
There's no existing evidence
of him having a family.
No posts, no pictures, nothing.
And all of his friends
and former co-workers,
they all said the same thing.
They don't know anything.
Is that possible?
Aren't you just paranoid?
You're a smart kid.
Think about it.
La Familia's peace was disrupted
when he entered the picture.
Now, if you're really concerned
about your mother,
think about what I'm saying…
before it's too late.
-Clara.
-Hm?
-Is Miss D in her office?
-Not yet.
She went out for a meeting.
She hasn't come back yet?
Not yet.
-All right, thank you.
-I'll be over there.
Hi. Yes.
I'm sorry, I was in the elevator.
Yes, I just got to the office.
Diana…
You should sober up first
before coming in.
Yes, don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
Okay, bye.
Uh…
Oh. Patricia.
What are you doing there?
You were with Mama?
And you had drinks? Is she drunk?
Yes…
We had a meeting outside the office.
The guest wanted us to drink
and we couldn't say no.
I noticed you and Mama are getting closer.
You're spending more time together.
Other people have been noticing as well.
You two are always laughing together.
Don't you want to see her laughing?
I want my mother to be happy.
But I'm worried.
Because as the saying goes,
"Too much laughter now
might lead to so much sadness tomorrow."
It's just a saying.
Is there something going on
between you and Mama?
Patricia…
I like Diana.
I'm not married yet. I'm single.
And your mother has been alone
for a long time.
So I don't see anything wrong
with us liking each other.
-Since when?
-Is there a problem with that?
Patricia…
You have nothing to worry about.
Your mother is important to me.
I'm not going to hurt her.
How about other people in your life?
What exactly happened
between you and your ex-partner?
I remember you told me
that you were never married,
but that doesn't mean you never loved her.
Why did you break up?
Let's just say that…
we weren't compatible in a lot of things.
We lived together for a few years,
but ended up separating.
Where is she now?
Don't you trust me?
Ah…
It's not that I don't trust you.
I just want to make sure
my mom won't get hurt again.
Because you're right.
My mother has been alone for a long time.
But not anymore.
She's no longer alone.
Because I'm back by her side.
Gosh, you would never take no
for an answer, Ricardo.
So, fine. I'll go with you.
You can stop nagging me.
Where are you, anyway? I'm here.
Okay, okay.
Oh, Patricia. Why haven't you gone home?
Want me to have Benjie drive you home?
No need.
-Are you sure?
-Papa will fetch me.
Oh, okay.
How about you? Are you going home?
Not yet.
You have plans with Sir Ricardo?
Yes. Patricia, is there…
Is there something you want to ask me?
Are you in a relationship
with Sir Ricardo?
You see, I talked to him.
He said he likes you.
We haven't gone public
because I don't want anyone
putting meaning
into our relationship
since we still work together.
But, Patricia… I'm happy.
If that's the case, that's good.
I just want you to be sure.
How about you? How are you and Enzo?
Are you happy? Are you sure about him?
Patricia, dear!
-Pa?
-Get in our car!
Diana, see this?
I've leveled up now. I've got a car.
I can fetch Patricia now.
She no longer needs to commute.
Good.
I'll be off now.
Bye, dear.
-Let's go?
-Yes.
Let's go, Pa.
Thank you.
That Ricardo is such a show-off.
Is he hitting on your mother?
Wait, why are you asking?
Because he's so full of himself!
He thinks he's all that.
Pa.
If they do end up together…
…I don't see anything wrong about it.
Do you approve of Ricardo for your mother?
As long as he doesn't hurt Mama.
I'll just clean the car.
Uh, P-Pa? By the way…
Um…
N-Nice car you got there.
Looks like you love it so much.
May I ask how you paid for it?
Is it fully paid?
Of course! It's fully paid!
That's the fruit of my labor!
And when my business grows,
I'll buy a brand-new one.
You've been quiet.
So, you told Patricia.
I just told her that I have
good intentions for you
so she wouldn't worry.
What did she ask about?
About my child and my ex-partner.
What did you tell her?
Diana, I think…
you're the only one
who deserves an explanation
because it's our relationship.
Besides…
it was just a one-night stand.
Although we had a baby,
we were never together.
Then, our child got sick.
You already know that, right?
But we agreed to keep
our relationship to ourselves.
Diana, are you ashamed of me?
Of course not.
But what if someone else finds out?
What if my critics
and detractors get wind of it?
I don't want you to be their next target.
Is that really the case,
or do you still have doubts about me?
I understand why Patricia
is overprotective of you.
But I'm not hiding anything.
I hope you understand.
Patricia and I are just starting
to get along.
I just don't want anything
or anyone to get between us again.
So, please…
help me find the person
who wants to bring me down.
So we can all be at peace.
Actually, I heard something about Teddy.
He's pestering Patricia.
He's trying to poison
your daughter's mind.
I think he's targeting Patricia
because he can't get near you.
Your brother has become desperate.
He's grasping at straws.
But don't worry.
I'll handle him, okay?
That might be important.
You're more important.
-Hi!
-Next time, just text me.
Don't call unless it's an emergency.
Diana almost caught me earlier.
Well, I'm sorry, okay?
You didn't call or text.
-I got worried.
-Sandra.
I can't afford to give them
any reason to doubt me.
Patricia's starting to ask questions.
I assume you managed
to appease her curiosity.
Yes, but she's still suspicious.
Too bad. She might just
be the one to thwart your plans.
All good to go.
Thank you.
Hm? I know that look.
Is something bothering you?
I get that you're concerned.
Dear…
No matter what happens
between Ricardo and me,
we will face it.
We've made this decision together.
And wherever this leads…
we'll be responsible for ourselves.
I get that.
I just want you to be sure
about Sir Ricardo.
Ricardo told me…
that Teddy is pestering you.
I think Uncle Teddy has a point.
We still don't know everything
about Sir Ricardo.
Especially about his personal life.
Dear, he's a very private person.
I know he had a child,
but he never had a relationship
with the mother.
Oh.
-Hi.
Let's go? We're running late
for our lunch meeting.
Okay.
I'll see you later, dear. We have to go.
Hmm?
Dad? Dad.
Dad! Wake up, Dad!
Dad!
You haven't settled last month's
electricity bill.
Now, we have a disconnection notice.
-Have you seen this?
-I'll handle it.
Hey! I can't even talk to you properly!
Have you seen yourself?
See?! Dad, you're obsessed!
-You're still on to Ricardo?
-I will exterminate that pest.
I know he's the vermin
that's infesting La Familia.
Hello?
What did you find about Ricardo?
Diana! Diana, please!
-Teddy, what is it this time?
-Please, listen to me.
I found something about Ricardo.
Teddy, will you stop it? My--
Just take a look at it, please.
Someone took a photo of him
with a Quick Bites staff.
Please.
That's proof.
I'm not the spy.
I'm not the one planning
La Familia's downfall.
It's Ricardo.
Think about it. The reporter,
the attack against you,
the poisoning, it wasn't me!
Ricardo was the one behind all of it.
Now, did you find
strong evidence against me? No.
This is proof.
Are you going to let yourself
be fooled by a man again?
Send me the picture.
I'll have it investigated.
Let's go, Benjie.
Miss D?
Have you asked an expert
about the photo yet?
Yes, Miss D.
They already checked
the file data and image details.
They found no signs
that it was digitally altered
or AI-generated.
The image is authentic, Miss D.
The thing I asked you to do…
Where's the driver?
As per our logistics manager,
the driver went AWOL
after he gave his testimony
against Sir Teddy.
To this day, he still hasn't returned.
They don't know where he went.
Good thing we finished early.
Hey, let me drop you off.
Don't you think Sir Ricardo
has something to do
with the threats against Miss D?
Why would he do that?
Where was he again when the fire happened?
That was in 2008.
Wait. It should be on his CV.
Uh…
It says here that he was working
at a PR firm in Indonesia
during that time.
We're not going home just yet.
Huh?
Excuse me.
-Is the doctor in?
-Yes, sir. He's on his way.
You're such a kind son, Sir Ricardo.
Your mother is lucky
to have a son like you.
-Thank you.
-I'll take you there, sir.
Okay.
Enzo, did I hear that right?
He's going to visit his mother?
Uh…
Let's follow him.
Patricia, wait!
I can't see clearly.
Patricia, he'll see us!
We followed Sir Ricardo
to the hospital, Miss D.
He was looking after an elderly woman.
Who was the old lady
he visited at the hospital?
His mother.
What? I--
Enzo, remember?
I had you check his background.
Exactly, Miss D.
And that's what surprised me.
Because based on the information
I gathered about him,
both his parents were declared deceased.
Why are you with
the executive of Quick Bites?
I did my own investigation.
I talked to this person to find out if…
it's true that Teddy's
conspiring with them.
That's one of the files
in Teddy's investigation.
But I'm still verifying it.
That's not all.
Your personal details
on your resume don't add up.
What are you talking about?
It states there
that both your parents are dead.
Who are you visiting at the hospital then?
Are you having someone tail me?
I need to know the truth.
Those are personal details.
I can't help but be suspicious.
Lately, your actions have been suspicious.
You're talking to someone on the phone
but you won't say who.
And now I found out…
you're still hiding something
about your life.
When my mother died…
someone took care of me.
She treated me like her own son.
So the information you got is correct.
I visit my mother at the hospital.
But not for long.
Her time is running out.
I didn't mention it to you because…
I just want us to be happy
when we're together.
Who told you this?
Was it Teddy?
Patricia?
Diana, I understand you
because they're your family.
So you should believe them.
Do you have any more questions?
Okay.
Was it wrong of me to ask?
Was what I did wrong?
I just wanted to protect
the interests of the company.
And I hoped that…
my own brother didn't betray me.
So you believed
Ricardo was the one scheming all this?
Do I always have to choose
between two things?
I know that Ricardo is upset with me.
But I can't help but be suspicious.
I've been betrayed many times
by the people around me.
You're just scared.
Is it wrong of me to be suspicious?
You're scared of yourself.
Of your own feelings.
When you sense something wrong,
you dwell on it.
You're scared of giving Ricardo a chance.
You're scared of making mistakes again.
Have you seen Ricardo?
I don't think I've seen him today, Miss D.
Oh.
Diana, can we talk?
Excuse me.
My resignation letter.
I know I still have
to render 30 more days.
Correct?
Why?
Diana, I can't stay in a place…
where no one trusts me.
Well, if that's your decision,
there's nothing I can do.
Just make sure that the turnover…
to your replacement…
goes smoothly.
Hello?
What?!
Wh--Why? What happened?!
Huh?!
All right, nurse. I'll be on my way.
Uh… Wh-What happened?
I have to go.
M-My mother needs me at the hospital.
Enzo!
Miss D? Everything okay?
Where did you follow Ricardo?
What hospital?
At St. Gabriel Hospital.
Call Benjie.
Tell him to get the car ready.
-Right now. Hurry!
-Okay, Miss D.
Ricardo.
Ricardo, I'm so sorry.
I'm very sorry.
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
What's her name?
Mama Esther.
Is there anything I can--
Anything I can do?
-How can I help?
-Don't.
There's no need, Diana.
I can handle this myself.
Go home.
Where's Miss D?
She was in a hurry to leave earlier.
She went to see Sir Ricardo
at the hospital.
Why? What happened?
Sir Ricardo resigned.
Maybe it's because of that.
Sir Ricardo resigned?
Oh, where are you going?
To the hospital.
Hey.
Nurse, where's the patient who was here?
What's your relationship to the patient?
Um…
I'm acquainted with her son,
Ricardo Salvador.
How's the patient?
She just passed away earlier.
Oh… Is that so?
Why are you also wearing black?
Well, I guess we're the only ones
who can mourn her.
She's pitiful, isn't she?
She doesn't have any family.
Yes, right.
Oh, yes, I am.
Did they mention any plans for the wake?
No.
What do you mean, no?
But I heard earlier
that they will bring the ashes home
after the cremation.
-Thank you.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
All my files
related to La Familia are in here.
I'll leave them here for now.
If that's not enough,
just let me know.
What's your plan now?
I'll leave it to fate.
I'm sure there's still a job
waiting for me in Indonesia.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I just want to know. How are you?
I still care about you, Ricardo.
I do, too.
I still care for you.
My feelings for you
will never go away, Diana.
I just don't want to force it anymore.
Maybe Patricia really doesn't
want me to be with you.
That's why she still won't stop
investigating me.
Maybe it's because…
my explanations to you
still aren't enough.
I didn't ask Patricia
to do anything like that.
The person who died
was like a mother to him.
Won't they hold at least a mass for her?
Doesn't she have any relatives?
Why does she have
to be cremated right away?
Patricia.
Ma.
Didn't I tell you to stop investigating?
-But, Ma--
-Ricardo just lost someone.
He's grieving.
Does he have to explain
everything he does?
He's in a very difficult situation.
Please stop asking him questions, okay?
Am I understood?
-Yes, Ma.
-Thank you.
Just leave them on my table.
I'll just go see Ricardo.
Okay, Miss D.
Yes, I'm just taking care of something.
But I'm on my way.
Same restaurant?
Okay, I can't stay long, okay?
Okay.
Benjie, get the car ready.
I'm coming down.
Reservation for Sandra?
-This way, sir.
-Thank you.
-Hi.
Did you fix it already?
Mh-mm.
Ricardo.
Diana.
Ricardo was the one behind all of it!
Teddy, will you stop it?
The way he kicked Uncle Teddy out…
It's like he's having fun with it.
-It's Sir Ricardo.
-What about him?
He's like a different person.
How can we prove
that what he says is true?
I won't force myself
on someone who doesn't love me back.
I tried to stop it.
I've never felt this way before.
I want to prove my love for you.
Diana, will you marry me?